http://circlesaw.com/privacy-policy-for

My Cart: 0 Items
($0.00)
3M Abrasives
Adjustable Clamp Company has Closed the doors effective May 19, 2016
Granberg International
Great Lakes Custom Tool Mfg., Inc.
Newsletter
Email Address:
Click here to unsubscribe
My Cart
Your Shopping Cart is Empty
Privacy Policy for
PRIVACY POLICYYour Privacy on circlesaw.comThis policy covers how circlesaw.com treats information you give us when you use this website. circlesaw.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes that we make.Collecting InformationWe may collect the following information:• Full name• Contact information• E-mail address• Telephone # becomes your internal account number to improve record keeping• Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests• Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersWe will never sell, lease or share your information with parties outside of Circle Saw.  CookiesWe may set and access 'cookies' on your computer. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyses web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.What we do with the information we gatherWe gather this information to understand our customers’ needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:• Internal record keeping.• We may use the information to improve our products and services.• We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.• From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.• We may contact you by email, phone or mail.• We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.Your InformationYou can edit your circlesaw.com account information at any time. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the circlesaw.com Newsletter. You can opt-out at any time. We will not send you our newsletter unless you have signed up for it. Confidentiality and SecurityWe limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.Protecting Your InformationWe do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies. We may provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of circlesaw.com but this is very rare. These companies may use your personal information to help us communicate with you about offers from us. We may share information to respond to legal matters, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law. We transfer information about you if circlesaw.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event we will notify you before information about you are transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
We use Paypal as our payment processing service and they operate under their own terms and conditions as well as their own privacy policy. It can be found @ https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full
Manufacturers
Please select
3M Abrasives
Adjustable Clamp Company has Closed the doors effective May 19, 2016
Great Lakes Custom Tool Mfg., Inc.
